"You are invited to an anonymous online meetup
exclusively for romance-bot owners."
An email from an unknown sender...
"On the day of the event, please enter using
the URL below."
If I attend this, maybe I can learn where
Nadeshiko came from?
"ENTER"
Aha, you made it!
Welcome to the owner meetup!
Huh?
This feels so... ordinary!
So is yours a girl too then, Miss Miaka?
Huh? Oh, y-yeah!
Mine too!
Check out this pic! It came out so pretty!
Huh...?
What sort of girl is yours, Miss Miaka?
Well, her name is Nadeshiko...
Is this girl... really a robot?
Her frame doesn't have any
mechanical parts at all.
- It's almost like...
- Miss Miaka!
Yes?
Nadeshiko looks totally adorable!
And like she might start
speaking at any moment!
Yeah, but there are so many girls
who aren't so good at the talking thing.
So then... Nadeshiko's...
no ordinary romance-bot after all!
I didn't learn jack!
And the most shocking thing of all...
"My doll hobby got so intense that
I became a humanoid robot fanatic☆"
Apparently I'm the only pervert
out there having sex with their robot!
I'd hoped to learn a little
more about Nadeshiko...
I could tell you all sorts
of things if you'd like.
Like about, say...
About your body.
Akane...
What's going on?!
Nadeshiko copied herself?!
Is she secretly a ninja-bot?!
Oh, Akane...
I love you.
I can't explain it, but...
having her whispering in
both my ears feels so good~
You said you wanted
to know more about me.
So I thought I'd introduce you to my
virtual functions you hadn't seen yet.
So then this black Nadeshiko is... virtual?!
Exactly!
The sensation of being licked...
Of being sucked...
Are reproduced almost 100%.
You see? I'm not actually
even touching you anywhere.
But it's not enough for
me to simply sit and watch.
Wait! I—
It's her same old tricks again!
Hey, Akane?
What were the other
romance-bots like?
Oh, I got some photos.
You want to see them?
Brought to you by ToonsHub
Yes, please!
This image...
I wonder if she noticed my little message.
It's been so long since
I've seen dear Nadeshiko.
I'm suuuper looking forward to it!